Can you lick something close to your body?
体の近いも舐められる?
stretch your knees
膝を伸ばして
Will it fit in your lap?
膝 の中に入るかな?
膝の中に入るかな?
Will it fit in your lap?
It's kind of small.
なんかちっちゃいもんね
...
Can you stand on your knees?
膝 を立てられる?
膝を立てられる?
Why don't you move your hand towards me?
手をこっちに押しに向けない?
Kneel up?
膝を立てる?
it's okay
大丈夫だよ
Or bend your body forward.
も しくは体を倒して 前に倒して
I started wanting to come from behind.
後 ろからきたくなってきちゃった
I feel like it's going to be a mess.
め ちゃくちゃしまっていっちゃいそう
Can I take it out like this?
この まま出していい?
It was really good
めちゃくちゃよかった
how was it?
どう だった?
it was fun
楽しかった
What do you think?
どう ですか?
Sorry, good night, I want to try again. One more time?
ごめん おやすみさまさ もう一回したいよ もう一回?
I want to try it again. Can I try it again?
もう一回したい もう一回していい?
Is it okay?
いいの?
open?
開ける?
Look into my eyes
目見て
I'll clear your throat
喉 出すよ
Sorry
ご め
Hmm.
ん ね
See you bye bye
また ね バイバイ